okay so what does wine mean to you all
of our
our memories with wine are the most fun
amazing
parts of our love story with me and
duane you know uh
gosh we were in central pay and he had
arranged for this
private wine tasting like it was like a
tour of french wines
and uh the freaky things we did after
that tasting it's usually like where the
wine
takes you and that was uh it's one of
those ones that you think back
kind of gives you a little shiver um
yeah yeah
that one that wine led to some some
breakthroughs it was uh it was a good
time
oh this has some bubbles to it okay is
this a champagne
i was keeping it in italy don't they
have champagne in italy
wrong country phoebe i'm from ohio you
guys i just thought you could get
champagne
there's detroit's champagne
caviar gap oh oh okay hold up
we're gonna do a good old bump ah
we're doing caviar bumps this is kaluga
so it has this nice
buttery hazelnut flavor this is the
caviar daniel kahlula what is this
kaluga
[Music]
listen you guys i have three glasses of
wine i'm
definitely drunk
my did i mess up amaze
do you think i'm going to be completely
wasted by the end of this
oh you guys
i'm just gonna what is it can i eat this
it's a sausage
[Music]
okay so child what you got for us we
have
a blend and we're going to talk more
about structure same thing
yeah into the swirl all right gabby i
see you swirling
and then we go ahead and smell okay
here's the thing whenever people tell me
sniff red wine i like don't smell
anything i'm like
people are always like it's a okie or
it's like a
you know redwood i'm like how do you
know these trees i have no idea
it smells like a good time to me go
ahead and taste it's jammy
okay i'm just just want to sober up just
a little bit so i'm just gonna
just have a nothing
cause i got to keep this classy on
comedy central